Hi.
안녕.
Well
음
my battery is only at 10% but
배터리가 10%밖에 남지않았는데
the reason I suddenly turned on the live is
갑자기 라이브를 킨 이유는
today
오늘
actually yesterday
어제
like I sent on Fromm I bought
그 프로에 보냈듯이 화장품을
some new makeup and
새로샀는데
I tried using them
화장품으로
for the first time.
이제 첫 게시해 봤거든요.
But
근데
I really love it.
너무 마음에 들잖아.
Ah so
아,그래서
I turned it on.
껴봤어요.
The makeup
화장
colors are so nice today.
오늘 색감이 너무마음에 들어 가지고.
I also tried putting in hair extensions by myself today.
오늘 머리도 제 혼자 한번 붙여보고.
Doesn't my makeup look pretty good today?
오늘 메이크업 좀 괜찮지 않아요?
Is it bad?
별로요?
In real life
시물은
it's a bit more
조금 더
how should I put it
뭐라 해야 되지?
it's not
이렇게
exactly this
뽀용하진
bright and pastel
않고
it's actually
조금
a bit more muted.
약간 좀 뮤트해요.
But I guess the
근데 여기가
colors aren't showing up well here.
책감이 잘 안 보이는 거같아.
Today it's like this
오늘 이렇게롱
Today
오늘은
I'm not wearing contacts.
렌즈 안 꼈어요.
These are my bare eyes.
생눈입니다.
Ah
아
I really like it
마음에 드랑
so today
해서 오늘
I came
나메이크업
to brag about
잘됐다고
how well my makeup
자랑하려고
turned out.
왔어요.
The point of today's makeup is
오늘 메이크업의 포인트는
pink.
핑크.
Now our comeback
이제 우리 컴백이
is only
이틀밖에
two days away actually.
안남았잖아요. 사실
The reason I still haven't
지금 왜 옷을 아직
changed my clothes is because
안 가려고 있냐면
I still have practice left.
연습이 남아있거든요.
I have to go to practice.
연습 가야 돼요.
Practice is
연습이
still
아직
Since I still have to go practice
연습하러 가야 돼서
I
이제
put these clothes on but
옷을 입었는데
I really just came to brag.
진짜 자랑하러 왔어요.
I just loved my makeup so much today
그냥 오늘메이크업이 너무 마음에 들어서[웃음]
Am I feeling okay?
몸은 괜찮냐고요?
Of course. Medicine
그럼요. 약을
medicine and
약이랑
IV drips
수액이랑
Ah medical science is
아 역시 의술이
truly amazing.
대단해.음
Should I give a
이번
spoiler for the title track?
타이틀 곡 스포 한번 해 줄까?
What is there?
뭐가 있지?
What could there be?
뭐가 있을까?
I don't think I can there are already too many spoilers.
안 될 거 같다. 너무 스프가 이미
But we've already revealed a lot.
근데 공개 많이 했잖아요.
If we
이제
reveal
더 이상
any more now
공개하면은
I feel like there wouldn't be any anticipation.
어 기대감이 없을 것 같아.
But seriously the title track
근데 진짜 비타민 B는
gets better the more you listen to it. Everyone
들으면들을수록 좋습니다. 여러분,
I haven't gotten sick of it yet.
아직까지안 질렸어요.
When I first heard it
처음 들었을 때
I was like oh
오
it feels like this
이런 느낌인데
but as you keep listening it becomes like oh
듣다 보면 오
this is even better.
더 좋은데 약간 이렇게 돼요.
Among this album my favorite track
이번 앨범 중에 최고캐트릿
is so good.
너무 좋아.
The song is slightly
약간 좀 노래가
chilling you know?
선늘하거든요.
I really love that chilling vibe.
그 선늘한 느낌이 전너무 좋아요.
I really love it.
너무 좋아.
Really love it I love it so much.
너무 좋아. 너무좋아.
It's the exact mood I like.
내가 좋아하는 분위기.
It's kind of
약간
very bright but
되게 밝은데
very eerie.
되게 섬뜻해.
Spooky.
섬짓.
I really love that about it.
그게 너무 좋아요.
Actually
사실이
In the Mirror
터널를
seems to be the one Flovers are looking forward to the most.
플로버들은 제일 기대를 많이 하시는거 같더라고.
But
근데
personally rather than In the Mirror I prefer
난 개인적으로 이터널보단
Prom Night.
포켓트리
With In the Mirror
이터널이랑
I'm still getting close to it.
아직 친해지고 있는중이에요.
I'm shy so it's still awkward.
낚가리고 아직 어사
We're still awkward but
아직 어사인데
we're getting closer.
친해지고 있어.
But I like them all.
근데 다 좋아요.
Honestly
진짜
I
제가
usually
원래
when preparing for an album
전국
like this all the songs
이렇게 앨범준비할 때
when I'm doing makeup or listening to music
뭐 화장할 때나 노래들을때
uh
어
from the title track to the b-sides
타이틀 곡은 들어도 수로까지
I just keep
막 이렇게 정을
playing them on repeat.
계속 반복해서만거든요.
But this time
근데 이번에는
I really
진짜
find myself constantly listening to it. Like all the tracks
계속 듣게 되는 거 같아. 이렇게전곡
from track 1
1번부터
to 10 constantly
10번까지 계속
on loop
뺑뺑이로
while doing my makeup.
화장하면서
Since it's been a while
오랜만에
since I put in hair extensions
이렇게 머리를
like this
붙이면은
it feels really unfamiliar.
되게낙설어요.
My hair is too long.
머리가 [목을 가다듬음] 너무 길어.
Since my
나
hair had gotten short
머리가 짧아졌다 보니까
it feels awkward having it long again.
길어진게 어색해.
After Prom Night
포켓트릿
the next best song is
다음으로 좋은 거
Don't Care.
티첩
Ah as for
아 대원은
Eye Contact
대원은
it's excluded
재회
because that
이거는
would be too
너무
biased of a decision.
편파 판정이 돼요.
Since I wrote it.
내가 쓴거니까.
Of course
당연히
because
내
I wrote it I want to tell you to listen to my song a lot. But
내가 쓴 거니까 내 거많이 들어 주라고 하고 싶지. 하지만
since that's a biased decision
편파 판정이니까
just
그냥
based on my actual taste I really love Prom Night.
진짜로 취향으로 따지면 진짜포켓트릿이 너무 좋아요.
Don't Care is really good too and
티처도 진짜 좋고
the title track is definitely good of course.
[콧방귀] 타이틀 곡이 확실히 좋긴하지.
All the members
멤버들이
really
다들
loved it. As soon as they heard it.
너무 좋아했어요. 듣자마자.
My Night Routine.
마이라미.
Mm.
음.
Ah all the songs are good everyone.
아, 노래 다 좋아요, 여러분.
Bring It On is good and they're all good.
블라트도 좋고 다 좋아.
Why did I do full makeup today?
오늘 왜 삶했냐고요?
I just
그냥
wanted to.
하고 싶었어.
I bought new makeup so
화장품 샀는데
if not at times like this
이럴 때 아니면은
I wouldn't have a chance to try it.
사용해 볼 일이없으니까.
TikToks too
땅땅땅도
originally that
원래 그거
what was it?
뭐지?
I was going to shoot a Reel but
릴스 찍으려했는데는
uh this
어 이거
I wanted to post it but
팔라했는데
definitely
확실히
I think I need to go to the shop
샵에 가서
and have the stylists
쌤
uh I think I need to go to the shop
그
do it before I film it.
샵 갔다가 찍어야 될 거 같아이지
I heard this is an AI song?
이게 AI 노래라면서요?
It's my first time
여기서
turning on a live from here right?
라이브 킨 건 처음이죠.이
This mirror
거울은
is the one
이제 전 숙소에서부터
I brought all the way from our old dorm
가져왔던
back then.
그때
It's that light. I brought all the way from our old dorm
그 조명이에요.
That light
그조명을
is familiar right?
익숙하죠?
It has a slightly cool tone.
그래 조금 쿨한 느낌.
So
그래서
my face might look even prettier in it.
얼굴은 이게 더 이뻐 보일 수도있어.
Because it's cool-toned.
쿨에서.
In the
옛
past
옛날에
when I
막 제가
ate croffles
플러프 먹고
and ate braised kimchi
김치찜 먹고
and did all that
했던
it's that mirror.
그거울이에요.
Do I eat croffles these days?
요즘에 플러프 먹어요.
I think I posted a picture of me eating a croffle recently didn't I?
최근에 플러먹은 사진 올렸던 거 같은데 아닌가?
Kimchi
김치
I'm really into kimchi jjigae
나 요즘 김치찌개에
lately.
빠졌어.
Not braised kimchi
김치찌 말고
but I fell for kimchi jjigae
[웃음] 또 김치찌개에
again.
빠졌어.
It's just so delicious.
너무 맛있는 거잖아.
Kimchi jjigae
김치찌개
with extra ramen noodles
라면살이 추가해서
you know when you just order kimchi jjigae. In that
그냥김치찌개가 왔잖아요. 거기에다가
put it in a pot. Then add the ramen noodles. Then add
냄비넣어요. 그다음에 라면 사리를 넣어.그다음에 라면
just about half of the ramen soup powder.
스프를 살짝 반 정도만넣어요.
It's seriously so delicious when you eat it like that.
그런 다음에 먹으면 진짜맛있어요.
It's so good.
너무 맛있잖아.
But guys coming back to life after being sick
근데 아팠다가 살아나니까 여러분
it makes a person
사람이
just
막
really
진짜
grateful.
감사해져요.
like really
막 진짜
I
나
called our manager crying at dawn
새벽에 울면서매니저님한테 전화했다니까
asking them to save me.
살려 주세요.
Because my mom and dad weren't answering their phones.
아니 엄마 아빠가 전화를 안 받는거야.
At like 2 or 3 AM.
한 새벽 2시인가 3시에.
Ah
[헉 소리]
honestly
진짜
it was so miserable
너무 서럽고
I wanted to whine to my dad but
아빠한테 땡강부려야 되는데
being alone
혼자서
you can imagine how sad I felt.
얼마나서럽겠어요
Everyone
여러분
seriously
진짜
it's really hard being sick alone. Even the wet towel
혼자 아프면 진짜 힘들어 물수건도
I
내가
had to it's really hard being sick alone. Even the wet towel
직접
prepare and do it all myself had to
해 가지고 직접 해야 되고
seriously guys
진짜 여러분
don't get sick when you're alone.
혼자 있을 때 아프지마세요.
This is
여기는
the perfume and
향수랑
bag
가방,
glasses
안경,
and accessories room.
악세방이에요.
So there are a lot of perfumes
그래서 여기에 향수들도
here too. The perfumes
굉장히많아요. 그때 소개해졌던
I introduced last time
향수들도
are here too.
있고요.
Ta-da. There are perfumes like this. And
짠. 이런 향수들도 있고요.이
this perfume too.
향수도 있고요.
Lately I've been spraying this perfume
요즘 저이 향수
a lot like this.
이렇게 많이 뿌려요.
My taste
취향은
I think my taste just kind of
제 취향은 그냥 여기서 약간
stopped here.
멈춘 거같아요.
It's so good.
너무 좋아.
I love it. But
너무 좋아.데여
I think it's better to wear it
겨울에
in the winter. This is
하는게 더 좋은 거 같아.이거는
this is
이게
Devotion
디버션
Eau de Parfum.
오드 퍼.
It's a perfume but
향수인데
it's a bit
약간
heavy.
무거워요.
But the lingering scent is so good.
근데 [목을 가다듬음] 잔냥이 너무좋아.
A bit lighter
좀 가볍게
in the summer
여름에는
seriously this
진짜 이게
isn't an ad.
광고 아니다.
I bought it with my own money.
내돈 내산이다.
Does it look better with my hair grown out? Looking at it like this
머리 기름게 낫나? 이렇게 보니까 또
I think it might look better grown out.
기름게 나은 거 같기도 하고
You see this right here? These
여기 보이죠? 이거
short hairs of mine.
내 짧은 머리들.
Or is it better short?
싫은게 낫나?
But
근데
I can just go back and forth
뭐 왔다 갔다 하면서
with it anyway.
하면 되니까요.
The clothes I'm wearing right now
지금 입고 있는 옷은
you're right.
맞아요.
They are newly
새로
purchased clothes.
장만원 옷입니다.
Pretty right?
이쁘죠?
What time is it now?
지금 몇 시지?
5% left. 5%.
5% 나왔어. 5%
Alright
자
then
그러면은
at exactly 15 minutes
딱 15분에
anyway I just wanted to brag
아무튼 오늘 메이크업 잘됐다고
about my makeup turning out well today.
자랑하고 싶었어요.
There's no other
그냥 별
special meaning.
의미는없고.
And also since it's D-
그리고 또 D -
2 just two days away now
2 이제이틀 전이니까
I was
우리
going to ask you
노래 많이 사랑해달라고
to give our songs a lot of love
하고 오려고
before I leave.
했지.
Please give our songs a lot of love.
우리 노래 많이 사랑해 달라고요.
Since it's
이번
a full album this time
정규니까
our members are really
우리 멤버들 진짜
working so hard.
열심히 하고 있어.
Anyway
아무튼
I'll be going now.
저는 이제가 보도록 하겠습니다.